Guide to the John L. Margrave academic papers, 1952-1995 MS 505
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Meetings, 1970-1988, 220856
  - CBTCUS, April 20, 1978, 221271 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - CBTCUS, March 9, 1979, 221270 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - CBTCUS, October 19, 1979, 221269 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - CBTCUS, October 24, 1980, 221268 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - CBTCUS, December 4, 1980, 221267 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - CBTCUS, January 27-28, 1983, 221266 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - CBTCUS, April 29, 1983, 221265 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - CBTCUS, April 26-27, 1984, 221264 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - CBTCUS, October 25-26, 1984, 221263 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - CBTCUS, January 24-25, 1985, 221262 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - CCR, November 2-4, 1981, 221261 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - CCR, September 28-30, 1982, 221260 (Box 18, Folder 23-24)
  - CCR, October 2-4, 1983, 221259 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - CCR, September 23, 1984, 221258 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - CCR, October 7-9, 1985, 221257 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - CCR, December 12, 1985, 221256 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - CCR, April 3-4, 1986, 221255 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - CCR, February 10, 1987, 221254 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - CGS, November 29-December 1, 1972, 221253 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - CGS, December 4-6, 1974, 221252 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - CGS, December 8-10, 1976, 221251 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - CGS, February 18, 1980, 221250 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - CGS, December 1-3, 1982, 221249 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - CGS, November 3, 1984, 221248 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - CGS, Temple Evaluation, February 11-13, 1976, 221247 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Chemical Congress of the North American Continent, 221246 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Chemical Institute of Canada, 221245 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Chem. Lecture, 3M, 221244 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Chem. Lecture, Abilene Christian (also see Welch Foundation, Lectures), 221243 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Chem. Lecture, Baylor University, 221242 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Chem. Lecture, Berkeley University, 221241 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Chem. Lecture, Case Western Reserve, 221240 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Chem. Lecture, Columbia University, 221239 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Chem. Lecture, East Texas State University, 221238 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Chem. Lecture, Georgia Tech, 221237 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Chem. Lecture, New Mexico State University, 221236 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Chem. Lecture, North Texas State University, 221235 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Chem. Lecture, NRL, 221234 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Chem. Lecture, Oklahoma ACS, 221233 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Chem. Lecture, Penn. State University, 221232 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Chem. Lecture, Purdue University, 221231 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Chem. Lecture, Stanford University, June 4, 1979, 221230 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Chem. Lecture, Stanford/University of New Mexico/Livermore Lab., April 21, 1981, 221229 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Chem. Lecture, Stanford University, February 12, 1986, 221228 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Chem. Lecture, Stephen F. Austin, 221227 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Chem. Lecture, SUNY-Stony Brook, 221226 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Chem. Lecture, Syracuse University, 221225 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Chem. Lecture, Texas A&M University, 221224 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Chem. Lecture, UC-Davis, 221223 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Chem. Lecture, UCLA/Cal Tech., 221222 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Arkansas, 221221 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Chicago, 221220 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Colorado, June 24-July 3, 1975, 221219 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Colorado, October 2, 1980, 221218 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Connecticut, 221217 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Delaware, 221216 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Florida, 221215 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Houston, 221214 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Nebraska, 221213 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of North Dakota, 221212 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Texas, 221211 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Toledo, 221210 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Chem. Lecture, University of Utah, 221209 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Chem. Lecture, UT-Austin, January 16, 1974, 221208 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Chem. Lecture, UT-Austin, October 9-13, 1978, 221207 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Chem. Lecture, Vanderbilt University, 221206 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Chem. Lecture, West Texas State University (also see Welch Foundation, Lectures), 221205 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Chem. Lecture, Yale University, 221204 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Chemical Society, May 10-14, 1972, 221203 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The Chemical Society, December 10-11, 1973, 221202 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Chrysler Corporation, 221201 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Central Intelligence Agency Panel, 221200 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Colloque Weyl VI, 221199 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Continuing Education, May 9, 1974, 221198 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education, November 14, 1974, 221197 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - DARPA, September 23, 1983, 221196 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - DARPA, CDR/Hughes Tool, May 17-19, 1983, 221195 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - DARPA, High Pressure Technology Workshop, September 21-22, 1981, 221194 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - DARPA, Hughes Dry Lubricating Program, October 4-5, 1978, 221193 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - DARPA, Hughes Rolling Bearing, October 8-10, 1980, 221192 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - DARPA, Hughes Rolling Bearing Report, March 7, 1979, 221191 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - DARPA, Hughes Rolling Bearing Report, October 10, 1979, 221190 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - DARPA, Low-Density Workshop, July 5-6, 1984, 221189 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - DARPA, Materials Processing in Space, July 1984, 221188 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - DARPA, Self-Propagating High Temperature Synthesis, October 21-23, 1985, 221187 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - DARPA, Solid Lubricant Review, September 1, 1982, 221186 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - DARPA, Space Based Space Surveillance, September 19-23, 1983, 221185 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - DeBeers (Photographs of South Africa), 221184 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - DOE, Basic Energy Sciences Review, October 14, 1981, 221183 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - DOE, Electrochemistry of Carbon, August 17-19, 1983, 221182 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - DOE, Gasification Contract, June 25-27, 1985, 221181 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - DOE, Gasification Projects, June 22-24, 1982, 221180 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - DOE, Pittsburgh Energy Technology Center, April 22-23, 1986, 221179 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - DOT, Polymeric Materials, 221178 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Dow-Corning, December 13, 1983, 221177 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Dow-Corning, September 17, 1985, 221176 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - DTST, Briefing, 221175 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Du Pont, February 7, 1973, 221174 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Du Pont, April 3, 1973, 221173 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Du Pont, October 17-18, 1974, 221172 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Du Pont, February 12, 1975, 221171 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Du Pont, March 9, 1987, 221170 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Electrochemical Society, October 5-9, 1975, 221169 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Electrochemical Society, October 9-14, 1977, 221168 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Electromagnetic Containerless Processing, 221167 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Energy Advisory Council, November 17, 1975, 221166 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Energy Advisory Council, February 10, 1977, 221165 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Energy Forecast Conference, 221164 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Energy Research and Development, 221163 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - EPA, Chloroflurocarbons Panel, February 19-20, 1987, 221162 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - ERDA, Thermodynamics and Electrochemistry, May 18-20, 1977, 221161 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ERDA, University Conference, November 3-4, 1975, 221160 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - EREF, February 1, 1977, 221159 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - EREF, Board of Directors, June 16, 1978, 221158 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Exxon, 221157 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Faraday Society, 221156 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fluoridation, City Council, 221155 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fluoridation, Correspondence, 221154 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fluoridation, Miscellaneous, 221153 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fluoridation, Panel Questions, 221152 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fluoridation, Participant Papers, 221151 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fluorine Chemistry Symposium, 221150 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fluorocarbon Research Program, 221149 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - GA Technologies, 221148 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - General Electric Professors' Conference on Materials Science, 221147 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Goodrich Tire Company, 221146 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Gordon Conference, August 7-11, 1972, 221145 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Gordon Conference, July 22-26, 1974, 221144 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Gordon Conference, August 4-8, 1975, 221143 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Gordon Conference, August 23, 1976, 221142 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Gordon Conference, August 7-11, 1978, 221141 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Gordon Conference, July 26-30, 1982, 221140 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Gordon Conference, July 23-27, 1984, 221139 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Gordon Conference, August 12-16, 1985, 221138 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Gordon Conference, August 10-14, 1987, 221137 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Grambling, Grants Resource Development, 221136 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Gas Research Institute, 221135 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Houston-Galveston Area Council, 221134 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - High Temperature Chemistry Conference, 221133 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - High Temperature Facilities, May 17-19, 1976, 221132 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - High Temperature Facilities, November 28-29, 1977, 221131 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Houston Power and Light, Nuclear Power in Texas, 221130 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Houston Space Biotechnology Center, January 29, 1986, 221129 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Houston Space Biotechnology Center, February 20, 1986, 221128 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Hterm [High Temperature] Conference, 221127 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Hughes Aircraft, August 1, 1978, 221126 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Hughes Aircraft, March 6-7, 1979, 221125 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency, 221124 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - IBM Research Lab, 221123 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - IIE Council of Graduate Schools Advisory Committee, 221122 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - International Conference on Chemical Thermodynamics, 221121 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - International Conference on Matrix Isolation Spectroscopy, 221120 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - International Conference on Refractory Oxides, 221119 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - International Symposium on Fluorine Chemistry, 221118 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - International Symposium on Organosilicon, 221117 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - International Union of Applied Chemistry, 221116 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - International Union of Pure Chemistry, 221115 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Space Research, 221114 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Jet Propulsion Lab, Electronic Field Positioning, 221113 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Jet Propulsion Lab, High Temperature Technology Advisory Committee, 221112 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Joint Venture, Cal Tech, 221111 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Kincaid Career Day, 221110 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Kincaid School, 221109 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Kiwanis Club, Solar Energy, 221108 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - KUHT Radio and Television, 221107 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Lamar University, Energy Seminar, 221106 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Lasers (including a history of the laser), 221105 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Livermore Lab, January 26, 1976, 221104 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Livermore Lab, May 23, 1976, 221103 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Livermore Lab, February 25, 1980, 221102 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Livermore Lab, February 22, 1984, 221101 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Livermore Lab, June 28, 1984, 221100 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Livermore Lab, April 22, 1985, 221099 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Livermore Lab, November 1, 1985, 221098 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Livermore Lab, February 11, 1986, 221097 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Livermore Lab, March 26-27, 1986, 221096 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Livermore Lab, CRR Review, September 18-20, 1984, 221095 (Box 21, Folder 23-25)
  - Livermore Lab, CRR Review, May 1, 1985, 221094 (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
  - Livermore Lab, Research Program Review, August 18-19, 1977, 221093 (Box 21, Folder 28-29)
  - Livermore Lab, Review Panel, June 11-12, 1975, 221092 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Livermore Lab, Review Panel, August 10-11, 1975, 221091 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Livermore Lab, Science Research Program, June 10, 1976, 221090 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Livermore Lab, Technical Review, February 8, 1978, 221089 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Los Alamos, August 8-9, 1983, 221088 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Los Alamos, April 2-6, 1984, 221087 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Los Alamos, MST, July 30, 1985, 221086 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Los Alamos, MST Review, July 17-18, 1984, 221085 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Marshall Space Flight Center, Review, March 20, 1980, 221084 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Midwest High Temperature Conference, June 16-18, 1975, 221083 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Midwest High Temperature Conference, June 13-15, 1977, 221082 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Midwest High Temperature Conference, June 4-6, 1979, 221081 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous, 221080 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 12-16, 1972, 221079 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 11-15, 1973, 221078 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, 1974, 221077 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 16-20, 1975, 221076 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 14-18, 1976, 221075 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 1979, 221074 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 14-18, 1982, 221073 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Molecular Spectroscopy Symposium, June 11-15, 1984, 221072 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - MRC, April 12-13, 1979, 221071 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - MRC, July 5-31, 1979, 221070 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - MRC, Alternative Feedstocks, July 14-16 [1975?], 221069 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 5-28, 1972, 221068 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 2-27, 1973, 221067 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 1-26, 1974, 221066 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 7-August 1, 1975, 221065 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 5-29, 1976, 221064 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - MRC, ARPA, February 16-17, 1977, 221063 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - MRC, ARPA, July 5-29, 1977, 221062 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - MRC, ARPA, Energy Resources, July 20-21, 1972, 221061 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - MRC, ARPA, Epitaxy, July 12-13, 1976, 221060 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - MRC, ARPA, Epitaxy, July 12-13, 1976, 221059 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - MRC, ARPA, Very High Temperature Machines, July 25, 1975, 221058 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - MRC, DARPA, March 11, 1980, 221057 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 6-31, 1981, 221056 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 6-30, 1982, 221055 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 5-30, 1983, 221054 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 2-27, 1984, 221053 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 9-10, 1984, 221052 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 1-29, 1985, 221051 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - MRC, DARPA, July 29, 1985, 221050 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - MRC, DARPA, Advanced Fibrous Composites, July 19-20, 1984, 221049 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - MRC, DARPA, Carbon/Carbon Engine, July 26-27, 1983, 221048 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - MRC, DARPA, Ceramic Composites, July 14-15, 1983, 221047 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - MRC, DARPA, Electrochemical Energy Sources, July 11-12, 1983, 221046 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - MRC, DARPA, Emissivity, July 10-11, 1985, 221045 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - MRC, DARPA, Gas Integrated Circuits, July 6-7, 1983, 221044 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - MRC, DARPA, Laser Hardening, July 16-17, 1981, 221043 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - MRC, DARPA, Laser Irradiation, July 12-13, 1983, 221042 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - MRC, DARPA, Metallic Gases, July 11, 19, 1985, 221041 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - MRC, DARPA, Optical Coatings, July 6-7, 1983, 221040 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - MRC, DARPA, Organometallic Precursors, July 8-9, 1985, 221039 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - MRC, DARPA, Particle Beams, July 15-16, 1981, 221038 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - MRC, DARPA, Polymer Opportunities, July 22-23, 1982, 221037 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - MRC, DARPA, Polymer Research, July 15-17, 1985, 221036 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - MRC, DARPA, Space Materials, July 25-26, 1983, 221035 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - MRC, DARPA, Tribology Workshop, July 23-24, 1985, 221034 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - MRC, DARPA, VLSI, July 21, 1985, 221033 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - MRC, Plasma Etching, July 5-27, 1978, 221032 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Material Research Society, 221031 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NAS, April 21-23, 1975, 221030 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - NAS, April 26-28, 1976, 221029 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NAS, April 25-27, 1977, 221028 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
  - NAS, April 22-25, 1979, 221027 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NAS, April 21-23, 1980, 221026 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NAS, April 27-29, 1981, 221025 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NAS, April 25-28, 1982, 221024 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - NAS, April 24-27, 1983, 221023 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - NAS, April 29-May 2, 1984, 221022 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - NAS, March 29, 1985, 221021 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - NAS, April 21, 1985, 221020 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - NAS, April 27-30, 1986, 221019 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - NAS, April 26-29, 1987, 221018 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - NAS, NRC Associate Program, August 28, 1974, 221017 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - NAS, NRC Postdoctoral Research Panel, February 22-23, 1972, 221016 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - NAS, NRC Postdoctoral Research Panel, February 27, 1974, 221015 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - NAS, Regional Roundtable, January 26, 1984, 221014 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - NAS, Roundtable, January 13, February 18, 1983, 221013 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - NAS, Thermodynamics and National Energy, June 10-12, 1974, 221012 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - National Water Resources Association, 221011 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - NBS, Applications of Space Flight in Materials Science, April 20-21, 1977, 221010 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - NBS, Beckett Symposium, July 23, 1976, 221009 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - NBS, Characterization of High Temperature Gases, September 18-22, 1978, 221008 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - NBS, Symposium on Thermophysical Properties, June 15-18, 1981, 221007 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - NBS, Symposium on Thermophysical Properties, June 15-18, 1981, 221006 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - NBS, Synchrotron X-Radiation, June 13, 1983, 221005 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - NCURA, April 28-30, 1982, 221004 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - NCURA, May 14, 1987, 221003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - NCURA, Problems in Research, March 30, 1978, 221002 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - NCURA, Support Opportunities, November 10, 1978, 221001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - North Texas State University, Conclave, August 13-17, 1978, 221000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - NRC, Associateship Program, February 21, 1973, 220999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NRC, Associateship Program, June 28, 1985, 220998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NRC, Associateship Program, February 25-26, 1987, 220997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NRC, Associateship Program Review, February 20, 1985, 220996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NRC, Associateship Program Site Review, August 24, 1978, 220995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NRC, Biomaterials Science, September 19-20, 1983, 220994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NRC, CODAN, January 28, 1977, 220993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NRC, CODAN, October 19, 1977, 220992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NRC, Committee on High Temperature Science, July 1984 (not the Margrave journal), 220991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NRC, Committee on Nuclear and Radiochemistry, April 29, 1988, 220990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - NRC, High Temperature Science, March 19-21, 1979, 220989 (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - NRC, Postdoctorate Associateship, February 26-27, 1986, 220988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - NRC, Postdoctoral Evaluation Panel, January 21, 1976, 220987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - NRC, Review Board, October 25, 1985, 220986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - NRC, STAMPS, May 20, 1977, 220985 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - NSERC, June 24, 1976, 220984 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - NSERC, January 5-6, 1977, 220983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - NSF, April 24-27, 1977, 220982 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NSF, Experimental Program to Stimulate Competitive Research, April 29-30, 1980, 220981 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NSF, Experimental Program to Stimulate Competitive Research, April 21-23, 1986, 220980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - NSF, Fellowship Program, 220979 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - NSF, Future of Research Programs, May 8, 1972, 220978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - NSF, Public Forum, December 9, 1975, 220977 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - NSF, Research Applied to National Needs, November 18-20, 1973, 220976 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Oak Ridge Gaseous Diffusion Plant, May 4-5, 1982, 220975 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Oak Ridge Gaseous Diffusion Plant, October 28-29, 1982, 220974 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - ONR, Esso Labs, May 16, 1972, 220973 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - ONR, Negative Ions, October 17, 1975, 220972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - ORAU, April 18-19, 1972, 220971 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - ORAU, October 20-21, 1976, 220970 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - ORAU, April 26-27, 1979, 220969 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - ORAU, Magnetic Energy Fusion, December 2, 1980, 220968 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Organometallic Chemistry Conference, 220967 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Organosilicon Symposium, 220966 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - ORNL, April 26-27, 1979, 220965 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - ORNL, Advisory Committee, 1970, 220964 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Oxide Conference, 220963 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Phillips Petroleum, 220962 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Photochemistry Conference, 220961 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Power Sources Symposium, 220960 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 220959 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Research Council, 220958 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Rice Center, 220957 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - St. John's School, Commencement, 1981, 220956 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Sandia Labs, March 1972, 220955 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Sandia Labs, December 4, 1974, 220954 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Sandia Labs, September 25, 1975, 220953 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Sandia Labs, January 19, 1981, 220952 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Science Advisor to President Reagan, 220951 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Science Alliance, University of Tennessee, December 1984, 220950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Science Alliance, University of Tennessee, December 1984 Science Alliance, University of Tennessee, May 6-7, 1985, 220949 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
  - Science Alliance, University of Tennessee, May 6-7, 1985, 220948 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
  - Science Alliance, University of Tennessee, November 17-18, 1986, 220947 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Scientific Research Society, February 8-9, 1986, 220946 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Second Annual Congress of the North American Continent, 220945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - SERI, August 29, 1978, 220944 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - SERI, High Temperature Sciences Workshop, November 28-30, 1977, 220943 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - SERI, Solar Repowering, August 2-3, 1978, 220942 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - SERI, University Panel, July 28, 1978, 220941 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sigma Xi, August 7, 1985, 220940 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sigma Xi, December 4, 1985, 220939 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Xi, February 20, 1986, 220938 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Xi, April 25, 1987, 220937 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Smithsonian Association (in conjunction with Sigma Xi), December 3-12, 1986, 220936 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Southern University Conference, 220935 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Southwest Electron Spectroscopy, 220934 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - The Space Foundation, May 17, 1985, 220933 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - The Space Foundation, June 19, 1985, 220932 (Box 26, Folder 19)